Finding Aid for the WSM Radio and Television Collection
Special Collections Manuscripts and Rare Books
- Photographs-1st Annual Pet Milk Talent Contest (Box 13, Folder 12)
  - 56) Unknown-fiddle, Unknown-Steel guitar, The Treys-microphone, Floyd "Lightnin" Chance-bass (Box 13, Folder 12)
  - 57) Ernest Tubb-guitar, Ray Edenton-guitar, Margie Bowes-microphone, Floyd "Lightnin'" Chance-bass (Box 13, Folder 12)
  - 58) Unknown-guitar, Ray Edenton-hidden, Ernest Tubb, Floyd "Lightnin'" Chance-bass, The Treys (Box 13, Folder 12)
  - 59) Ernest Tubb, Margie Bowes, Tommy Cutrer (Box 13, Folder 12)
  - 60) Hank Garland-dark suit, far left, Ernest Tubb-guitar, Margie Bowes, Glenn Johnson, unknown (Box 13, Folder 12)
  - 61) Gordon Stoker (Jordanaires)-far left, Ernest Tubb, Margie Bowes, Ray Edenton-guitar (Box 13, Folder 12)
  - 62) Jordanaires(2), Ernest Tubb, Margie Bowes, Floyd "Lightnin"' Chance-bass (Box 13, Folder 12)
  - 63) Ernest Tubb, Margie Bowes, Tommy Cutrer (Box 13, Folder 12)
  - 64) Ernest Tubb, Ray Edenton-guitar, (2) Treys (Box 13, Folder 12)
  - 65) Faron Young, Margie, Ray Edenton-guitar, Floyd "Lightnin"* Chance-bass (Box 13, Folder 12)
  - 66) Ray T.denton, Faron Young', Unknown, Maggie Bowes, Tommy Cur.rer, Floyd "Lightnin"' Chance (Box 13, Folder 12)
  - 67) Faron Young, Margie Bowes, Floyd "Lightnin" Chance-i,iss (Box 13, Folder 12)
  - 68) Ray 'Sdonf on. ".iron Youn«, v'-? Bows, Floydnjn Chance, Tommy Cutr (Box 13, Folder 12)
  - 69) 2 unknown men, unknown woman, Bob Cooper(WSM), unknown woman, unknown man (Box 13, Folder 12)
  - 70) 4 unknown men (Box 13, Folder 12)
  - 71) Front row; 3 unknown men Back row: 4 unknown men, Bob Cooper (WSM) (Box 13, Folder 12)
  - 72) Unknown man, Phil Craig, unknown man (Box 13, Folder 12)
  - 73) Emerson Pryor(WDVA), Sid Wolf, Bob Cooper(WSM), Tommy Cutrer, Bob Piggott (Pet Milk), edwin Peterson(Keystone); In front: 5 unknowns (Box 13, Folder 12)
  - 74) 3 unknown men, Edwin Peterson(Keystone), 2 unknown men, Sid Wolf, 2 unknown mei (Box 13, Folder 12)
  - 75) Unknown, Sid Wo1f, Unknown, Edwin Peterson(Keystone) (Box 13, Folder 12)
- Photographs-2nd Annual Pet Milk Talent Contest, 1959 (Box 13, Folder 13)
  - 1) 3 unknown women, Ernest Tubb, Tommy Cutrer (Box 13, Folder 13)
  - 2) 2 unknown men, 3 unknown women-at piano (Box 13, Folder 13)
  - 3) Tommy Cutrer, 2 unknown women, Edwin Peterson, unknown woman (Box 13, Folder 13)
  - 4) At microphone: 3 unknown women and [Wilbum Brothers?] Far right: Tommy Cutrer (Box 13, Folder 13)
  - 5) 2 unknown men at microphone, [Little Jimmy Dickens?], Tommy Cutrery (Box 13, Folder 13)
  - 6) 3 unknown women, 2 unknown Ln-on steps (Box 13, Folder 13)
- Photographs-3rd Annual Pet Milk Talent Contest, 1960 (Box 13, Folder 14)
  - 1) Jordanaires(4)-seated; Pete Drake-steel guitar; Hank Garland-electric guitar; Jimmy Day-steel guitar; 3 unknowns, Tommy Jackson-fiddle, Ray Edenton-guitar; Cathy Morrison, Bill Morrison; 3 unknowns; Tommy Cutrer-microphone; Teddy Wllburn, Doyle Wilburn (Box 13, Folder 14)
- Photographs-4th Annual Pet Milk Talent Contest, 1961 (Box 13, Folder 15)
  - 1) Jim Dodge and Ken Runyon (Box 13, Folder 15)
  - 2) Bob Cooper, Jim Dodge-with plaque (Box 13, Folder 15)
  - 3) Unknown man, Bob Piggott, Jim Dodge (Box 13, Folder 15)
  - 4) Bob Piggott(Pet Milk), Cliff Thomas(WSM) (Box 13, Folder 15)
  - 5) 'Unknown-guitar, Tommy Cutrer, Roy Acuff (Box 13, Folder 15)
  - 6) Bill Gentry, unknown woman-guitar, Roy Acuff (Box 13, Folder 15)
  - 7) Unknown woman and man putting up sign (Box 13, Folder 15)
  - 8) Faron Young and Bonnie Rose Martin of Vidalia Georgia (Box 13, Folder 15)
  - 9) Cliff Thomas and Ralph Hartinagel with straw cowboy hats (Box 13, Folder 15)
  - 10) 2 unknown men, Bob Piggott(Pet Milk)-behind podium (Box 13, Folder 15)
  - 11) Bill Gentry, unknown, Ray Pillow, Jim Dodge (Box 13, Folder 15)
  - 12) 5 unknown men in white jackets, Jim Dodge (Box 13, Folder 15)
  - 13) Bill Gentry, unknown man, Bill McDaniel, unknown man, Jim Dodge (Box 13, Folder 15)
  - 14) 0the11 Sullivan, Unknown woman, Bill McDaniel, Bill Gentry, Jim Dodge (Box 13, Folder 15)
  - 15) Sid Wolf, Ken Runyon, Bob Cooper, Bob Piggott (Box 13, Folder 15)
  - 16) Sid Wolf, A1 ? (Box 13, Folder 15)
  - 17) Unknown man, Ruth Dodge, Jim Dodge (Box 13, Folder 15)
  - 18) Jim Dodge, Ruth Dodge (Box 13, Folder 15)
  - 19) Bob Piggott, Jim Dodge (Box 13, Folder 15)
  - 20) Bob Piggott (Box 13, Folder 15)
  - 21) CF Roberts,. Johnny Rose, Jim Dodge (Box 13, Folder 15)
  - 22) The Grell Family, in background-Cliff Thomas pointing finger (Box 13, Folder 15)
  - 23) Othell Sullivan-with plaque, unknown woman, Jim Dodge (Box 13, Folder 15)
  - 24) Unknown woman, unknown man, Bonnie Rose Martin, Jim Dodge, Bob Piggott-behind podium (Box 13, Folder 15)
  - 25) Allen ?, Ken Runyon, Jim Dodge, Bob Cooper (Box 13, Folder 15)
  - 26) Johnny Rose, Roy Acuff (Box 13, Folder 15)
  - 27) Johnny Rose with guitar (Box 13, Folder 15)
  - 28) Johnny Rose, C.F. Roberts (Box 13, Folder 15)
  - 29) Johnny Rose, C.F. Roberts (Box 13, Folder 15)
  - 30) 4 unknown men at podium (Box 13, Folder 15)
- Photographs-Various (Box 13, Folder 16)
  - 1) Roy Acuff, photographer [Old Hickory Lake] (Box 13, Folder 16)
  - 2) Roy Acuff, unknown man, TCX 1tt €> IT (Box 13, Folder 16)
  - 3) Military band and troops at train depot [194?] (Box 13, Folder 16)
  - 4) Stage with band, military speaker [l94?] (Box 13, Folder 16)
  - 5) Broadcast News Awards (Box 13, Folder 16)
  - 6) Camel Caravan at Parthenon, Nashville, Tennessee [194?] (Box 13, Folder 16)
  - 7) Camel Caravan performing for troops [194?] (Box 13, Folder 16)
  - 8) Company Band, Camp Jackson (Box 13, Folder 16)
  - 9) June Carter[?] (Box 13, Folder 16)
  - 10) unknown, Bill Clairborne-in WSM studio? (Box 13, Folder 16)
  - 11) Patsy Cline (Box 13, Folder 16)
  - 12) Francis Craig-2copies (Box 13, Folder 16)
  - 13) Francis Craig and Orchestra (Box 13, Folder 16)
  - 14) Francis Craig and Orchestra; Francis Craig-far left, Dinah Shore-seated on pia (Box 13, Folder 16)
  - 15) John DeWitt, Jr. (Box 13, Folder 16)
  - 16) [Ohio River Flood, 1937?] Unknown man on house, 4 unknown men in boat (Box 13, Folder 16)
  - 17) [Ohio River Flood, 1937?] two unknown men in boat by gas pump (Box 13, Folder 16)
  - 18) John Gordy and the Dixielanders [Hank Snow on banjo?] (Box 13, Folder 16)
  - 19) Snooky Lanson (Box 13, Folder 16)
  - 20) Unknown man, Cliff Thomas, Ray Pillow (Box 13, Folder 16)
  - 21) Radar screen (Box 13, Folder 16)
  - 22) Radar screen (Box 13, Folder 16)
  - 21/22 Supplement: explanation of contents of radar screens (Box 13, Folder 16)
  - 23) Tex Ritter, Pester Wagoner, Grant Turner-Studio A, 5th floor National Life Building, Nashville, Tennessee (Box 13, Folder 16)
  - 24) Johnny Tillotson, unknown man (Box 13, Folder 16)
  - 25) unknown man-piano, Dinah Shore (Box 13, Folder 16)
  - 26) Soldiers loading truck (Box 13, Folder 16)
  - 27) Audience watching "Sunday Down South" [radio program] (Box 13, Folder 16)
  - 28) Audience watching ["Sunday Down South"? ] (Box 13, Folder 16)
  - 29) Audience watching["Sunday Down South"?] (Box 13, Folder 16)
  - 30) Orchestra for ["Sunday Down South"?] (Box 13, Folder 16)
  - 31) Audience watching ["Sunday Down South"?] (Box 13, Folder 16)
  - 13-16 Photographs-Various (Box 13, Folder 16)
  - 32) Audience watching ["Sunday Down South"?] (Box 13, Folder 16)
  - 33) Orchestra for "Sunday Down South"?, [June Carter?] at microphone (Box 13, Folder 16)
  - 34) Troops in action, composite picture (Box 13, Folder 16)
  - 35) Audience at hangar [194?] (Box 13, Folder 16)
  - 36) WHBQ-2 unknown men (Box 13, Folder 16)
  - 37) Front row: 5 unidentified girls (sisters?) Back row: unidentified man, Cliff Thomas (Box 13, Folder 16)
  - 38) Front row: 5 unidentified girls (sisters?) Back row: 3 unknown men, Jim Dodge, Edwin Peterson, Sid Wolf (Box 13, Folder 16)
  - 39) [WSM executives?] (Box 13, Folder 16)
  - 40) [WSM executives?] (Box 13, Folder 16)
  - 41) [WSM executives?] at dinner (Box 13, Folder 16)
  - 42) [WSM orchestra?] (Box 13, Folder 16)
  - 43) Faron Young on paddle boat [Old Hickory Lake?] unknown people on dock (Box 13, Folder 16)
  - 44) Unknown man and woman (Box 13, Folder 16)
  - 45) Unknown man and woman 13-12 Photographs-1st Annual Pet Mi X k T31 ent Contest, 1958 (Box 13, Folder 16)